techairlines.com 2010-12-31

# Privacy Policy - TechAirlines

This privacy policy states how Tech Airlines collects and uses your information and is current as of August 16, 2009.

### What information do we collect?

We do not collect any personal information without your knowledge. We receive your email address and name only with your explicit consent, such as contacting us. In order to prevent spam, your email address is required to post any comments. Your IP is automatically logged when you leave a comment.

Some products and sites we link to may require registration which may require information like your Name and Email Address. In this case, please refer to the site’s own privacy policy.

We do not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 13. If it is found that we have data from a child under the age of 13, we will remove the information, whether its public or private, immediately. Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to register on our forums.

### IP Addresses

Your computer uses an IP (Internet Protocol) Address each time you connect to the internet. An IP address is a number and logical address identifying devices in a computer network that connects to the internet. Your IP is automatically collected when you leave a comment and post in the forum.

### What are “cookies”?

Your Internet browser has a feature called cookies, which stores small amounts of data on your hard drive about your visit to websites. You are free to turn it off in your browser options however some sites may not function properly. You do not need to have cookies turned on to visit our site. Cookies cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive and pass on malware.

### How do we use cookies?

Like most websites, our site uses cookies. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent here, referring sites, and other traffic data. On our site, cookies help us find out how our visitors use our site and what areas are most popular so we can work on improving. However, no personally identifiable information is ever sent to us or intentionally stored in your browser in the form of cookies.

Cookies will also prevent manipulation of poll results.

Cookies are not required to be enabled to visit our site, although some parts of the site might not work properly. Most browsers have them on by default however if you choose to disable them, this can be done in your browser options, usually under ‘Privacy’ or ‘Security’.

### How do we use the information you provide to us?

Any information you provide to us will only be used to contact you and will not be shared with any third party unless required by law. If you provide it to subscribe to our feeds via Feedburner Email Subscriptions, you are agreeing to [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy.html), as the information will be stored and processed through Google. You will receive an email when there’s a new post and no more than 1 email a day. We have access to this data and you can request us to remove you from the list anytime. As always, we will not share this data with anyone.

### Do we sell, share, lend, or otherwise give out your information?

We will never share, lend, sell, or otherwise give out your information, including email addresses, to any third party unless it is required by law. We will never use your information for any marketing purposes.

### Links to Third Party Websites

Our site contains links to third party websites. When you use these links to other websites, please note that we have no control over other websites and therefore, our Privacy Policy no longer applies. Please refer to the Privacy Policy of the applicable website. This privacy statement only applies to sites on the techairlines.com domain and all subdomains.

### Changes Made to this Policy

This privacy policy may be modified from time to time. It is not likely to be a major change, however you should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are satisfied with the changes. The date this statement was last modified will always be stated at the beginning.
